cannot satisfy all my desserts by
overcoming the nature of desire
it's it's it's very much related to the
previous question that you had about
suffering basically set B what people
deem to be satisfaction of their desire
it's the result of the desire so by
pursuing the set what you think
satisfaction is cannot possibly satisfy
the desire in the sense of making go
away it only covers it up so and and
feeds it more because the desire is
rooted in in again in your mental in
your mental attitude
which means if you were to remove the
desire from its roots there won't be
anything there to satisfy there will be
no pressure for you no nothing no burden
for you to have to chase and reach this
goal and satisfy this displeasing
feeling of an unsatisfied desire but you
can't that's what people don't realize
you can't satisfy the displeasing
feeling of our nonsense for desire you
can only cover it up with a pleasing
feeling of a non satisfied desire desire
remains unsatisfied the desire the goal
of desire is not to be satisfy the goal
of desire is to perpetuate its own
nature of being a desire that's why
whether you're resisting pain or giving
into pleasure you are maintaining the
nature of your desires so your
yes you can either suffer because the
circumstances are displeasing and you're
trying to change them
or you can remove your desire to go to
the Caribbean and then you're at peace
because you don't want to go in the
first place